Wojciech Dominiak

Junior frontend developer

City: Poznań

Phone: (+48) 601-319-466

E-mail: wojciech.dominiak96@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://wojciechdominiak.github.io/
Github: https://github.com/wojciechdominiak

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/wojciech-dominiak-96w/



My interest in programming started back in 2012 in middle school. Since then programming has been my hobby and I've also used it as an engineer in my work. As my master thesis, I wrote a simple desktop application in Python for commercial use. Now I've decided to expand my knowledge. I've been learning modern frontend development for about one year. I've gained knowledge of advanced math e.g. logic, analysis or algebra during my studies. I've been working creatively with customers for two years. Currently I'm looking for a commercial job as a programmer.

Projects

https://github.com/wojciechdominiak/find-coaches

Stack: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Vue.js 3.0 (Vue CLI, Vuex 4.0, Vue Router), Firebase.

https://github.com/wojciechdominiak/dragon-slayer

Stack: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Vue.js 3.0.

https://github.com/wojciechdominiak/remember-me

Stack: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Vue.js 3.0 (Vue CLI, Composition API).

Skills & tools

Programing Languages

HTML5, CSS3/Sass, JavaScript (ES6+), TypeScript, Python

Libraries & Frameworks

Vue.js 3 (Vue CLI, Vue Router, Vuex 4.0, Composition API)

• Tools & Platforms

VScode, Git, Github, npm, npm scripts, prettier, ESLint, Webpack, Babel

Experience

SECO/WARWICK - Junior mechanical designer

12/2021 - present

Sieć badawcza Łukasiewicz IPS "TABOR" - Junior mechanical designer

09/2020 - 11/2021

Education

Poznań University of Technology - M.Eng - Mechanical Engineering

10/2016 - 07/2021

Languages

Polish - native

English - B2/C1